Jake Schlosser



Contact

- 309-238-3171
- Melbourne, FL
- jakeschlosser309@gmail.com
- Github

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

I'm a passionate self taught front-end web developer with 3+ years of experience using JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, and Tailwind to build all aspects of the user experience and user interface. On top of that, my development skills allowed me to build sites using Svelte, React, and SvelteKit. I've gained experience and used platforms including Docker, TablePlus, Supabase, and Github/lab.

Skills

- Tailwind CSS HTML / CSS
- Git Javascript
- Svelte / SvelteKit
- Responsive Design

Education History

SELF TAUGHT

- Udemv
- Freecodecamp
- Youtube
- W3Schools

Work Experience

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

Allstar Exterior Wash | 2021 - 2021 🔗



- Designed the layout.
- Maintained / added additional content and functionalities to the site as requested.

Mandolas | 2020 — 2020 🔗

- Built entire website from PSD mockups to finished site.
- Advised client on improved UI.

Disco! | 2022 - Present



• Create new pages/features for business and client facing websites using svelte(kit).

Fee Calculator | 2022 – 2022



 Built a custom calculator using Svelte & Supabase for a client to use for their business to help with efficiency.

Chino Valley Ranchers | 2022 - Present

- Create/Update frontend components from PSD mockups using React/Tailwind.
- Update main banner regularly.